Greening everyone.
Warm welcome to my session I know it's the last session of the day.
You...now I have at least.
One thing in common.
We all carry just one mobile phones...laptop.
And, we want to check both our facebook...and work
e-mail and reproductive on the same device how many of you do that here.
So, this poses a challenge or responsibility rather.
To those managing id and enterprises.
You need to ensure that...is like you and me.
Productivity and they can seamlessly use
...devices.
Whether they're at home or at work.
Ensuring that these devices do not compromise the security of your enterprise.
This is exactly why we need management of devices.
Mobile device management
is particularly useful when you need to manage users
that are mobile not just mobile devices so what do I mean by that
users who use their personal devices but also those who use
corporate devices and...mobile and are hardly connected to the corporate network?
Or if you are looking to move to the cloud.
...cloud-based management solution then mgm is your answer.
Still in a typical enterprise there are different kinds of devices we
have iowa's devices iphones android tablets windows stand tablets and
phones.
in this in this particular session I'm going to cover the tools that you require
the enterprise features that we're adding...that you can use to manage windows
ten devices and applications in your enterprise.
...by the amgen any lots of even and if you have any questions that
...not able to answer during the session are later in inside...you can fee for
...question to my twitter account and I'll make sure that I get back to you.
So, what...some of the challenges that we face
today...you face today when you management those devices?
We asked some
of the it pros and fortune hundred companies and this is what we heard.
You need more control to manage these mobile devices more and
more of these devices that are coming into the enterprise today
are mobile devices and why windows eight-point one
does have a rich level of mgm capabilities the
...of control that you need is much more and
something that's closer to group policy that that's available today for you for...
Second when managing windows devices
an enterprise today you have to
use different tools to manage different kinds of devices why do I mean by this.
During that windows phone eight-point when you can set a policies say
to disable camera to...and you can enforce this on the
windows phone devices however you cannot use the same
...policy to enforced.
Or disabling the camera on windows species so.
You would have to resort to a different tool like group policy
...system center configuration manager for the same.
Is an inconvenience to you because you now have to use different tools for different windows devices?
...because of this need to use different management tools for different
windows devices always a chance for policy conflict let's say the system center configuration
admin set the policy to disable the camera for pc's and
...exchange active...admin did not said the policy.
...ends up adding...exchange account...and up-and-up adding
...exchange account of my pc and it gets manage by both exchange active
...and also by system center configuration manager the
...are...expected the policy may not be enforced correctly
so now you have to have these...sync up with each other before the policies rolled out.
Finally.
Let's say you were able to figure out what tools to use for which windows device
...able to configure the policies without conflict.
...a user still...inconsistent user experience when I
try to launch the camera up on the phone I see a different error message and then I try to launch
camera on my pc I see something different when the admin has blocked the
use of camera so how are we moving to...the direction of addressing these challenges between
First of all we are expanding the mobile device management capabilities
beyond what already existed with windows, windows phone eight-point one
these mobile device management capabilities can be leverage by all
mgm servers and also existing tools like
system center configuration manager will see that in a minute how that's possible.
While the level of control we provide for windows stan will not be exactly the same as
...policy provides
for pc's today we are looking to what closing that gap moving forward.
Second all controls are all policies that
you set to m d n for windows
...will be converged they will and apply to all windows devices
in your enterprise if you can disable camera through
an emblem policy that will apply to all phones tablets or
...that are in your in your into price so it makes it much easier for the admin to
enforce one policy and see that applied...a quick...of that later.
Still
...be a case when you how you need to have multiple management tools managing your device
and this case the windows
stent device automatically resolve conflicts and picks the most
secure configuration when it is managed by more than one management to
so in the previous example that we saw even if the exchange active
...admin had disable the head...not...use of camera the more stricter
configuration that the system center configuration admin applied would take effect on
the device and finally because windows stand is a converse platform.
I now have a consistent
experience when a policies enforced on any of my windows device sign
summary all of these benefits put together make it easy to manage windows
...devices in the enterprise for the rest of this lights people
...keep an eye on all of these benefits and see what each of the features provides.
Windows hobby windows devices have
...enterprise for a really long-time so we understand that there are
lot of tools are management options that you already used today.
And, windows...makes management easy not just by expanding
mobile device management capabilities but also...by making sure that we
continue to support and enhance these existing management tools.
For example.
Today use active directory...on users to be
...species...you can continue to do the same between a
...will also be able to use agile active directory for the st.
Talking about management...of...still use group policies to manage
pc's you can continue to use that for windows stand devices and we
will be adding new group policies to support new windows...features for those
of you who use advanced group policy management or adpcm.
It will support windows stan and we're adding new publishable command let's that make
...and scripting easier for you.
Talking about system center configuration
manager its vitally used across enterprises for managing
pc's you can continue to manage pc's windows
...pc's using system center configuration manager
in addition all of the new mgm policies that we...for windows
stan the now also be available or can be leverage through
system center configuration manager I'll come to that...the next slide I promise?
For mgm.
In addition to the expanded...capabilities that I've been talking about there
is also support for initial provisioning of the devices which is going to make it easier
for you to...devices and bulk for your organization and other management providers like
exchange active saying bother shell or windows management
...continue to work for windows stent as the to do today.
So,...of these benefits possible how is the emblem
...designed let's take a quick.
I know this is kind of a busy...but I really want to highlight two key points here.
First any management tool that you pick for windows
...meet system center configuration manager or exchange active
...or mgm all of the configuration goes through
a common management layer of the bottom and so.
What happens is any configuration that you apply because of
...going through that common layer
the device itself is able to automatically result and pick the most secure configuration of the same?
Some center configuration manager uses windows management instrumentation
...to configure settings on a device and all of the new ambient features that we are
adding is added through configuration service providers that you see at the
bottom what we did was we added layer call the w my bridge to
our emblem stack so that we
could bridge the configuration service providers through doubly a
...and we're working very closely with the system
center configuration manager team so that they can leverage and configure all of
the settings that we're adding to mgm to system center configuration manager also.
So, what are these new features that we're adding to...n?
To illustrate this I would like to walk you through a story
r something that you go through every day in your
in your company so let's say I'm...new implying that's joining
your company you either make sure that you give me devices for me to work
...bring in my own devices which is actually becoming more popular nowadays.
You make sure that I have all the required things all the
require configuration to be productive at work.
And, at home or wherever I am and all this
time you ensure that my devices secular and the device the security of the
...also not compromised during the course of using the
...I'm going to have sometimes
...will have issues where I can call you and you'll be able to trouble
should those issues and finally...it's my last
data company you want to make sure that I no longer have access to any
of the corporate data or corporate resources that I had access to as an...
So, the first step that I did when I got these devices was
...to work and try and connected
to corporate wi-fi but I realized I couldn't do that.
It is because you require that I in...my device in
...n before I can...corporate wi-fi so that was really
the first step that I did I took my phone followed your instructions enrolled
...mgm server and picked up my laptop and
...back to look for the instructions.
But, what I find there was just one set of instructions for enrolling any windows
stan device?
This single enrollment experience for any windows
stand device really has to benefits one to me as
a user I just have to learn one way of doing it and
to-you as admins you just have to publish one set of instructions for any windows
...device.
...a hidden benefit here for...server vendors out there that they need to
implement against only one enrollment protocol for any windows...device.
So, let me show you a quick demo of how I enjoy my pc ensure...server.
And, by virtue of the experience being the same you would know-how to do that on the phone too.
So, here I have my device and based on instructions I navigate to settings
which is where our connect workplace setting is now and under
...ic work or school.
And, I see the connect but and I'm just going to click on it and enter the credentials that...has given me.
So, what happens when I
hidden continue here is my enrollment services auto discovered
based on the credentials that I enter for those a few that are using windows eight-point...a want
eight-point one this is similar to that and once my services discovered I see
the authentication page and this page is customizable for your enterprise if you want
to use multi factor authentication you could do the same or if you want to use one-time passwords
you could use that for instance microsoft we actually use a phone to
factor authentication so every time I sign in I have to verify that it's me on my phone before I
sign in for this demo it's basically just a password?
So, I entered the password and.
That's it so it was basically for
clicks and I'm and role within...server.
The...really simple and this is the same thing that we
have across all windows devices I'll show you a little bit later about how some of the policies are
applied to so I showed you how I enrolling to
...level but windows stand you have more options.
We talked...this at the beginning that
...stand you have the option to use agile active directory to log on users to your
...so you as my admin could mandate that I
...my device to agile active directory when I initially set up
the device because it's a corporate own device or I is
a user could choose to add and adjective directory account to
my pc after I set it up initially with my personal account.
That's going to give me single sign on to my corporate resources which is why am I
...add that so in both of these cases.
What happens with windows stan is that your device can be automatically and...with
...n when I connect to
agile active directory this is great because
india has the primary channel of management for agile active directory manage
devices just like group policy is for active directory manage devices so
you can ensure that my devices managed at the same time that I connect to
adjective directory plus I don't have to do these two steps separately?
Some of you also have the need to prepare or...provision devices for
...say...your financial group you want to make sure that they get their laptops
or they phones and when the unlocked phones are log
on to their laptops the system is already provision with the settings that you desire
...devices automatically enrolled with...server?
This is possible for windows stan using the bulk provisioning
feature where you can ensure that the devices automatically
enrolled without requiring user intervention and this is possible
by using certificate based authentication for the enrollment process itself
if you're interested to know more about bile provisioning and how we can help you
save initial setup time I would highly recommend reference session
this happens at ignite which is microsoft enterprise focus conference that happens next week
and chicago don't worry if you're
...all of the session recordings will be available online?
So, why did why did you ask me to enroll my device before I could
connective corporate wi-fi?
Because you could manage my device and ensure that I have all the things that I need
to be productive and the same time that my devices secure.
Windows...helps you do this to mgm by adding on to all
the rich features that we already had for windows and windows eight-point one through
All of the policies and all
of the configuration that existed will continue to move forward for windows stan.
Was available only on phones will now also be brought to pc's
wherever applicable in a quick recap of the windows eight-point one
...features I would suggest looking at the reference video here which is from the last
year's build.
The first thing that I saw when I...my phone was a message asking me to
set...for the device...
like this been policy you can now configure a lot of different policies
to mgm in each of these categories one notable addition that I want
to call out...the microsoft passport...
Some of you might have attended the session just before this where they talked about
passport microsoft passport is a feature in windows stan that
allows your users to move away from username and passwords to more secure and
easy and unlock procedures like fingerprint scanning or...bins and all of that.
You can also configure defender and...security through
mgm for pc's just like you could do it...group policy.
Here are some examples of policies that are available to mgm but this is
only a small sample set I couldn't put all the policies on here there are
over hundred new policies...adding for windows stand to...and this
is over the fifty policies that already existed for windows eight-point one.
So, let me show you a quick demo of how
icon figure the policy in one place
and the policies applied in a consistent manner on both my bc and...
So, here I have my pc that...and...with...
I going to settings just as I did before.
And, I see that it is enrolled.
With...observer
so my admin has set a few policies and let's see what those are
the first thing is...make sure that I'm not able to
...settings on the device that I useful work.
To my personal id so my divide my settings do not...across on
...species and I also c that madmen has.
Prevented me from removing my and role meant...I cannot on...my device this
is especially useful for corporate on devices where you do not want to users to
remove themselves from management and the other thing that I talk did that I just mentioned to you about.
Windows defender windows
defender is available on all on windows devices in-box the at my admin has
made sure that I cannot turnoff real-time protection because that would put my system
...so now let's move to my phone.
Which is...the exact same...observer?
That always has to happen during a demo.
So, I have my phone your and.
I'm going to navigate to the same place and look how the you why is
very consistent so I going to settings accounts worker school and I
see my device android I'm going-to try and then role its prevented.
I try to look at the
...my settings option that is also disabled so
...quickly also show you how...so I'm using microsoft into
...mgm server right now and you can see that
I've configured these policies and configured it as an windows
...policy not as a form or windows policy.
What has happened is the admin has been able to
configure the policy at once just for all windows devices and
it's in it's enforced on the devices on both my phone and the pc the
exact same way so this is what the converge platform and
one mgm solution is going to provide is going to give you for windows stent?
So, I finally android my device and I was able to connect to the
corporate wi-fi network which I wanted to but I
notice that when I connected to wi-fi I was not asked for my username and password.
My admin...provision the certificate for me to use for my by
phi authentication in windows eight-point one through n
...you could provision a certificate
using simple certificate enrollment protocol or skip as we call it so the
...server indicates to the device that it needs to go
unsaid get a certificate and the
...goes and gets a certificate from a skips of.
With windows stan in addition to this you will also be able to
installer certificate directly from...server by sending
the certificate along with the private key to the device without requiring the...
you may say that I want you to make sure I want you to strongly authenticate
before you use the certificate that is you want me to prove that it is actually
...who is using the certificate you can do this by
installing
a microsoft passport certificate devices through mgm.
So, now when I try to use my certificate I'm going to be
...shown the passport...need to enter the...or swipe my finger,
finger before I use it so you have to factor authentication there.
So, about two months back I was able to
connect wife evidence suddenly I was not the first thing that the admin
ask me to do was to check if my certificates
where installed properly I was able to do that on the pc with my certificate
manager app however how do I do this on the phone the certificate app that
is now available on the windows phone store allows you to do this
is extremely useful for troubleshooting issues and helps you view personal
...and intermediate certificates that are installed on your phone and it works both
with windows phone eight-point one and windows content.
I was able to connect to wi-fi and was
productive at work and it was though that time of the your when the
...great cloudy skies and redman got to me so I took a break and
hawaii as...was lying down in the be checking my email on my phone I
noticed a mail that asking me if I wanted to sign up for a
usability study of poland's I sure wanted-to and immediately click to the link but then I
thought this is an internet link it's probably not going to work.
But, it worked and I was able to successfully sign up for this study.
So, what my admin had done was...configured
or to connect and always on vp information so the minute I logged on to
might be laptop or unlock my phone there was a vp and connection may
to my enterprise and now I had access to all of the
internet resources just as I had when I was connected to corporate wifi?
The one difference with the windows always on
weepy and is that the users can decide to disconnected if they do not want to?
I closely looked at the car the vp and connections that my admin had
configured I notice that the at...different
...connection...was configured in such a way that only traffic from
...outlook one node and powerpoint could use that connection
so if I try to connect...over internet explorer it wouldn't use that
...and connection so what they had effectively done what's isolate
network traffic from certain enterprise applications over that
...and connection without me seeing anything any
I still had a seamless experience without me noticing any of that so with windows
...you can configure both and always...connect
bbn aspen is vp and traffic filters through mgm.
Furthermore the...and platform is completely...and it's
now open to third-party plugins for more information on windows...
vp and referenced video session from build is something that I would highly recommend.
So, we saw how we were able to control my access to both vp and,
corporate wi-fi based on if I was...with mgm or not but
wouldn't it be great if you can control access to corporate resources based on the
compliance state of my device let's say if it was not j broken.
So, with windows stan.
Going forward with conditional axis you will be able to control
access
to corporate resources based on the compliance state of the device the
...syllable can calculate...evaluate the compliance state of the device
based on a set of device attributes one key attribute that we're adding for windows
ten is the hardware attested device...state.
Think of this as something similar to j break detection that is available today
...non windows devices but provable in hardware using the
...we already have a cloud-based windows held at a
...service that is up and running for windows...devices to talk to
anime servers to rely on to know if a devices healthy or not.
But, windows...
Users device is going to be kept up to
date and current but for certain
enterprise devices you can manage how the devices are updated.
Just like you could do through group policy you can do this
through mgm now you can control when I scan and download
for updates and if I is the user should be notified about restart
just before dumped update completes you can also or to approve a set
of updates so that when I install the update I'm not asked to sign up
...assign on sign-off on the...or I don't see any user intervention at all.
Online devices that I've enjoyed I'm connected
to corporate wi-fi most of the time but a lot of the other times I made the connected to home
wi-fi or I'm on the goal so you can actually
configure how why install updates from do I hate the microsoft update
server over internet or do I install from the company update server or do
you want me to fallback if one is not available are the other?
We saw about update compliance...resolver compliance...the previous slide and
one key aspect that you want to use is update compliance.
Basically what that means is if a devices patched
...up-to-date with all of the updates that you want...device to be updated with.
For instance microsoft ensures that all security updates
been start on my device within seventy two...of release if not the devices
...non compliant so all of the information that you need to
make this decision about update compliance will be available through
mgm you can query which updates for successfully installed you can query which
of them failed or which of them are just spending a restart to complete installation?
So, do you see how all of these things so I enjoy my device I had to
...and igor of...and wi-fi connection certificates
to authenticate using and managing updates all of these are
designed to make me more productive but secure
the device but some of you may want to also make sure
the enterprise data on the devices secular in addition to the device been
secure I think of this as putting a log on your front door?
Vs locking every room in your house when
...avi so even if the devices compromised my
co data stay secure.
Enterprise data protection is a windows
...operating system feature.
That...markets
with personal and what data and keeps the work data secure?
Management of enterprise data protection is possible.
Through mgm and you can designate which data should
be considered as enterprise data that is which of the apps should be
considered as enterprise apps and how the data can be shared can-you copy
based content from a work document to a person document or do I have to
want the user are completely blocked them and
...doing this all of this can be configured through mgm?
I is the user over audio warning and still copied content from my work
...official well-documented facebook you can audit that and generate
reports of intentional data disclosure talking about apps.
Enterprise apps in the context of enterprise data protection you
can write apps that are aware of personal and work data.
To know more about how you can write enterprise data protection of
where applications
...a session tomorrow here at build that would be extremely useful for you.
So, we saw how my admin was able to
secular my device and keep my data secure but at the start of the top
...we said that the responsibility of the
...to prom and the second thing is that the
...the admin has to make sure that the users have a great ongoing experience
so windows stand has features that helps you do this effectively.
About a month back I lost my phone that was enrolled I looked for
it everywhere couldn't find anywhere I didn't set hadn't
...find my phone so I couldn't use that
to so I called up my ip they were able to remotely
find the location of my device through mgm.
Because it was somewhere in my work building I was able to look closer and find it.
Found that my...was...unfamiliar location they could have completely
wipe my device to prevent misuse of data.
This ability to completely vita device is now also available for
pc's especially for corporate own devices.
Some of you have the need to prepare devices say for
your marketing organization...use for...and demos it
is not guaranteed that the same device will be picked up every time so you
need to make sure that all of these devices have a familiar ui and consistent.
We know stent allows you to do this through mgm by manipulating the
...or changing this...screen the
start manual and also filtering out which apps can be used versus not.
Sometime after I enjoyed my phone iphone application called campus
experience that I had not instagram my admin had
install the application of my device michaela because they...it would be helpful for
...was helpful it helped me navigate through the confusing campus and
...sell applications are really backbone of any device I use one
node to take notes I use outlook to check my email I use the browser
app to stay up-to-date with current...with windows stan.
You can manage different kinds of applications through mgm.
The first thing to mention is that the app manageability platform for windows
...is converged across different windows devices and you
can now install delete update or query
both enterprise line-of-business applications...store applications through...
You can also install applications that can be used by multiple users
on a pc...specifically useful for share device scenarios.
Talking about site loading side noting is
the process by which you set up the machine for enterprise lb or
enterprise a line-of-business application install site loading is converged with
windows stand across all windows devices and I is the user can
unlocked the device from the why or you can unlock it through mgm.
The and the other two other things to note is that there's no limit on how many devices you
...and there's no requirement of internet in
terms of signing of the enterprise line-of-business application you can either use a
semantics certificate or specific enterprise signing certificate.
We talked about store applications but when thirty-two applications
are still widely used in pc's or I should say classic windows applications.
...windows...you can install
and manage msi based classic windows applications through...
And, apart from all of this life-cycle management you can also
set application restrictions to mgm so you can say which applications you want to
block from launching for the use of
or you can say which applications only should launch for the user.
And, this uses the family
our app locker technology that many of you may be aware of that existed on...
For a lot of deep information about application management
and enterprises I would highly recommend the session your by john
vincent which happens in ignite...here too if you have any questions later today.
So, the enterprise line-of-business applications are written in-house.
How do you acquire store applications distributed to your users through
...the business store allows you to do that for windows stent?
You can license what free and paid applications in bulk and distributed to
...either through mgm or instruct the user to
install it from the store using it...active directory account.
Let's say that you purchase tend licenses to a particular store application and push down the
aptly.
When I leave the company you want to make sure that you reclaim that license from
me and make it make use of it for someone else?
So, this license management is possible for windows
ten through mgm again for more information on
this specific topic reference session at microsoft ignite is a good resource.
So, you remember the week that I spend
...hawaii I decided that I just want to stay back so it's my last day in the company.
And, you is admins now want to make sure that I know longer have access to any of
the corporate resources that I had access to when I worked for the company.
Windows stand makes it easy for a
...the user or the admin to on android
for management and on enrollment removes all of the data
that was provision doing the life-cycle off management
...policies certificates wi-fi...profiles
or even applications and application data also the data that was tagged as
...under enterprise data protection is now completely removed
on enrollment.
So, we saw...during my demo that madmen had
...on enrollment right so in this case the admin will be the one
who controls when and if they...and they can do this remotely through...
For personal devices typically the users are allowed to unroll and when they do
unroll the server gets notified about it?
And, finally like enrollment
on enrollment also has a consistent experience across all devices.
So, those were some of the
...features that we're adding for windows stand.
And, I would take a moment to put a huge shout out and
a big-time q to all of our mgm server partners that we
are partnering width to make windows stand management extremely easy for you.
And, some next steps.
Please do download the windows insider preview
...and evaluate windows stand for your business talk to
...vendor to see which of these features you can test right now.
This is the right time for you to start thinking
about your enterprise application needs and start developing them.
And, finally please do let...your comments and feedback either rightnow person
right now in person are you can also use the windows user why sporty for the same.
Some resources for-you for both sessions
here and sessions at ignite next week.
These are all relevant sessions to enterprise that I think will be useful for you to look at
and are windows stand mgm documentation is available live on msdn
rightnow this contains all information about the protocols
configuration service providers that I was talking about the policies all
...and we are keeping it updated as and then we add new features to the upcoming
flights?
And, finally humble request to share your feedback about the session let us know
if it was useful and what else you would like to your...future sessions?
Thank you and I'll take some questions now and if in order to get to any of
the questions because it's the end of the day I will be...windows insider lounge
the second-floor tomorrow at eleven thirty...drop...you have any questions then to.
...a degrees.
So, is a question that can I push apps through the company, company help?
Yeah, so, domain join devices you can definitely
...them into...into any mgm so you can and role within mgm
you get the company portal and you can install...through that if you don't want to use sec and.
Any other questions.
That's a very interesting question I mean the question is currently unique only one user
can cel enrolling to mgm is their plan to support multiple
users enrolling so one of the things that I mean I didn't have enough time to cover but the whole
when I joined my device to agile active directory and I said that was the device
was automatically enrolled that is actually the device getting android so any
...active directory user that I log...width to that particular device is
...so...itself is managed so
that is really a powerful thing because for scenarios where you have you
need you need multiple users to be manage its typically in a corporate on device
you can actually managed to device and have every user on that logged in for by
already case we still think we still have a
...the limitation that you can have only one user and...
but that's because that's a typical scenario so it's my personal device and I'm the divine the user
...enrolling?
...here does if you have any app questions the deeper questions...
In that case so the question is if I have a desktop that's
...domain joiner have multiple users and I setter user level group policy what will
happen so the policy will apply only to that user so we have a concept
...device policy...a use...policy and that applies to all configurations like you
can actually have a vp and profile that is applicable to all users are only a particular
user and if it's configured as a user policy it only applies to that particular
if you think of a device like say let's say it's...adjective directly manage device I
have to users user one user to on it right so I
login as user one and if a policies applied for user one when I am logged in
ask that user that policy will applied but if let's say five login as user
to that user did not get the use...policy let's take the disable camera...easy if the
cameras disabled it will be disable for user one but it will not be for user
to but in a typical co-owner device scenario I think usually they want to
make sure...policies apply to all of the device
all the whole device and for all the users on that device so this we think is not a
common scenario but if you think that...there's there is something that you are
this is something that you use would love to hear about that one make sure that we get the feedback.
Check moi.
Excellent question we've done a lot of work for that the question is when you have a windows,
windows phone water woodwork the same so we have a windows, windows phone device that's
already...mgm...great windows stent what happens
the enrollment will be migrated and you will still be able to continue talking to
...server this is a critical scenario for us because the whole way that
the your update windows...going to be an upgrade...so we...make sure that this continues to work.
...see asking if all of this mgm will work without introducing domain
...group policy yes so this is
you can completely manager devices using
...without actually domain joining the device and like I said
...is becoming important because you still have now corporate devices that are hardly connected
to corporate network and which may not be able to domain join
...yes you can continue to manage using ambient without requiring domain...group?
And, also.
Is it possible...to?
Use the same...
Right and I would highly recommend tomorrow session because saw that's going to be very useful for
you so enterprise data protection and the question is like how do I is
it only the data or is it the apps also that's enterprise and
work for enterprise and personal and can a particular app operating both
...yes it council what typically happens is through the
mgm you can actually say this app is completely enterprise or if it's not specify the
can be completely personal but there are certain apps that
we call enlightened apps that can operate in both of these small it's like we are
...working on our...the office and all of that which is...be one of the critical
things and you can write applications that actually have this and enlightenment
so-you can we have different scenarios whereyou copy from a site that's mocked
...enterprise than that data when it comes on your device
it's going to be treated enterprise or when you generate data on your device that's the
most challenging part if it's generated from enterprise application it's all these enterprise but
...generated from and enlightened app I think there's, there's that there's a choice of the
...say but there is also another different way that you can say you can actually marked that
data as enterprise versus not so yes
...it is a critical it's something that we need for making sure that, you know,
we don't have...kind of completely labeled as enterprise...work so...the middle
...apps are something that's that will be...
So, I think it's tomorrow at eightthree thirty and it scarred
...building enterprise data protection aware applications.
So, those some of those skew decisions are still go
I'm going on right now so we don't have the complete information
right now on what's going to be supported where...that information will come so.
Any other questions.
Sure, go ahead.
Unknown so they will have to authorize that so think of...similar to a
smart card certificate if you've seen or which...smart card that if you use that so when you
install the certificate into your microsoft passport the user has to authorize that?
Any other final questions if not, you know, feel...drop a drop...law, you know,
if you have any questions...question through twitter...you can find...tomorrow on inside a
Great.
Thank everyone so you.